### Miles Falk

milesfalk@gmail.com

2004 Radiance Circle, Fairfield, Iowa, 52556 +1-(641) - 919 - 4752

# **Summary**

Dedicated full stack developer with 3+ years of experience in NodeJS, ExpressJS, Angular, Typescript, React, React Native, MongoDB, Mongoose, and Javascript. Extensive experience developing full-stack applications. I'm confident in my ability to master new skills and find innovative solutions.

## **Full-Stack Developer Skills**

Angular & Typescript
React & React Native
Nodejs & Expressjs
MongoDB & Mongoose
Redux
RxJS Reactive Javascript

NoSQL Databases
Javascript
Bootstrap & Jquery
Git & Github
Jest
NPM

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Full-Stack Developer (Freelance)**

Nov-2018 - Mar 2020

(Content creation and moderation platform, Admin CMS)

- Designed and developed two full-stack applications using MEAN stack technologies.
- Pivoted an existing code base to fit evolving requirements.
- Integrated many production quality API's, including Stripe, Twilio, and SendGrid
- Gained experience using Ng Zorro for UI design and AWS S3.
- Optimized performance by incorporating AOT compilation.

• Implemented a workflow management system to support various user-roles.

### **Full-Stack Developer (Freelance)**

August-2019 - Jan 2020

(Blog, Admin CMS)

- Designed and developed an application accessible to the public and another for admin to moderate site content (using MEAN stack technologies).
- Designed screen layouts with CSS3 and Bulma.

#### **Full-Stack Developer (Freelance)**

Feb-2019 - March 2019

(Technical Interview Screening Application for MIU's MSD Program)

- Developed a MEAN stack application for screening technical interview questions and ensuring the authenticity and integrity of answers.
- Designed the application to capture real-time user input and inform admin of their actions.
- Implemented Angular Material Design.

## **Education**

Maharishi School Fairfield, Iowa

Awarded a Scholarship to Attend Yale's International Young Scholar's Conference Singapore

Maharishi International University (Audited masters MWA) Fairfield, Iowa

We Think Code Bootcamp Johannesburg, South Africa

University of Johannesburg Robotics Department, Johannesburg, South Africa

### References

#### Dr. Keith Levi

Ph.D. Dean, College of Computer Science

Maharishi International University

Email: klevi@miu.edu Phone:+1-641-919-4451

#### **Asaad Saad**

Master's in Software Development, Program Director Assistant Professor of Computer Science Computer Science Department Maharishi International University

Email: asaad@miu.edu Mobile: +1-641-451-7070

#### **Rod Falk**

Computer Science Faculty Administrative Director

Maharishi International University

Email: <u>rfalk@miu.edu</u> Cell: +1-641-451-1146